Guide to the Margaret Wylie papers, 1926-1963.
Wylie, Margaret papers, 1926-1963.
- Series I. Cornell Study Clubs
  - Nassau County
    - County Leader: Mrs. Ruth Campbell, Mineola, NY, 1941-1942 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Inter-Community Family Life Study Club, Chairman Mrs. Helen Bowers, 1940-1941 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Mrs. J.J. Durfee, 81 Dover Pkwy., Garden City, L.I., 1941-1943 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Mrs. F.B. Taylor, 12 Mayfair Rd., W. Hempstead, NY, 1940-1943 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Family Life Study Club, Chairman Mrs. G.C. Bowers, Lynbrook, NY, 1944 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Mrs. Ruth Campbell, Mineola, NY, 1941-1942 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Niagara County
    - Home Demonstration Agent, 1933-1934 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Mrs. J.W. Moran, Lockport study club, 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Mr. Entorf's materials, 1935-1936 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Mrs. H. Scott, Niagara Falls study club, 1935-1936 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Mrs. Chas. Thomas, Lockport, NY study club, 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Mrs. Ralph White, Gasport study club, 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Home Bureau unit meetings, 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Johnson Creek Study Club, Mrs. Laura Davis, Gasport, NY, Chairman, 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Mr. Entorf, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Niagara County Child Life Forum Mrs. Howard Pickles, Chairman, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Niagara County Child Guidance Study Club; Mrs. Donald Gascoyne, Chairman, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Niagara County Parents' Guild Study Club, Mrs. Howard Ulrich, Chairman, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Niagara County, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Youngstown F.L. Study Club, Mrs. Margaret James, Chairman, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - May Truman, Federal Bldg., Lockport, 1940-1945 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Home Bureau, 1940-1945 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Child Life Forum, Niagara - Mrs. Harold Swanson, 76 Grosmere Rd., Lockport, NY, 1944-1945 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Cornell Extension Course, Chairman Mrs. Eva Metcalf, Lockport, NY, 1940-1945 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Lockport Child Discussion Group - Mrs. Wesley Puetz, 626 E. Ave., Lockport, 1944-1945 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Lockport Study Group,Chairman Mrs. Walter Schumacher; Mrs. Henry Taylor, Secretary, 1940-1945 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Mothers' Guild - Mrs. Robert Shutes, 22 Beverly Pkwy., Lockport, 1941-1945 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Newcomers Mothers - Mrs. John Zaremba, 99 South St., Lockport, 1944-1945 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Parents' Guild - Mrs. Raymond Schryver, 326 Chestnut St., Lockport, 1940-1945 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Oneida County
    - Mrs. Harry M. Fuess, Waterville, NY, 1931-1932 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Mrs. Arthur Pohl, Vernon, NY, 1931-1932 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Mrs. Merrel Rose, Oneida, NY, 1931-1932 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Home Demonstration Agent, 1930-1940 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Mr. Entorf's material, 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Mr. Entorf's material, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Home Bureau unit meetings, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Louise Weatherwax, Home Demonstration Agent, 1 Oxford Rd., New Hartford, 1940-1945 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Home Bureau, 1940-1945 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - (Untitled), 1940-1941 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Clinton Study Club, Chairman Mrs. Whitney Elliott, 1940-1941 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Onondaga County and Syracuse
    - Onondaga County (Syracuse), 1930-1931 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Mrs. Eileen Sehl Androus, Home Demo. Agent, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Mrs. J.D. Sands, Mrs. Carl V. Warren, Skaneateles, 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Mrs. Chas. Brown, Nedrow, NY, 1935-1936 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Mrs. Rockwood's material, 1935-1936 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Mr. Entorf's material, 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Home Demonstration Agent, 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Home Demonstration Agent, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Onondaga County, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Syracuse program, 1930-1931 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Miss Frances Scudder, Syracuse, NY, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Syracuse (Rockwood), 1935-1936 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Reports of unit meetings in Home Bureau Units, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Syracuse City Adolescent Study Club, Mrs. A.J. Paolini, Chairman, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Syracuse City, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Mrs. Eileen Androus, P.O. Bldg., Syracuse, 1940-1945 (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Home Bureau Reports, 1940-1945 (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - Hazel E. Reed, 408 Seitz Bldg., Jefferson St., Syracuse City, 1940-1945 (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - Syracuse City Home Bureau, 1944-1945 (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - Syracuse City, 1940-1941 (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - Ontario County
    - Canandaigua, NY, 1930-1931 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Mrs. Lavange Unger, Naples, NY, 1931-1932 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Mrs. Alice L. Wheeler, Home Demo. Agent, 1931-1939 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Mrs. James Horsfall, Geneva, NY, 1933-1934 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Mrs. Rockwell's material, 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Mr. Entorf's material, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Home Bureau unit meetings, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Home Demonstration Agent, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Mrs. Alice L. Wheeler, Court House, Canandaigua, 1940-1945 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Home Bureau, 1942-1945 (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - County Leader: Mrs. Harry R. Marble, R.D. #1, Holcomb, 1944-1945 (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - Orange County
    - Child Guidance Institute: April 17-18, 24-25; May 8-9, 1933-1934 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Mrs. L.E. Merrow, Middletown, NY, 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Miss Carrie C. Williams, Home Demo. Agent, 1932-1935 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Mrs. Henry Bull, Middletown, NY, 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Mrs. D. Leo Mack, Monroe, NY, 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Mrs. R. Swinton, Port Jervis, 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Mrs. C. Van Inwegen, Port Jervis, 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Mr. Entorf's material (Mary Switzer, Middletown), 1935-1936 (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Mrs. Gladys Geddis, Port Jervis, 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Mrs. R. Hill, Pine Bush, NY, 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Mrs. E. Velsor, Middletown, NY, 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Mrs. Grace Sly, Middletown, NY, 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Orange County 4-H, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Home Bureau unit meetings, 1938-1940 (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Mrs. Dorothy Barnes, Middletown, NY, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Mrs. Hollis O. Smith, Monroe, NY, 1938-1940 (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - Local leader training meetings, Orange County, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - Mrs. V.R. Baildon, Warwick, NY, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - Mrs. Margery C. Chardavoyne, Chamber of Commerce Bldg., Middletown, 1940-1945 (Box 31, Folder 34)
    - Home Bureau, 1940-1944 (Box 31, Folder 35)
    - Mrs. Dorothy Robbins, Middletown, 1940-1942 (Box 31, Folder 36)
    - Mrs. George Gibbs, 43 Houston Ave., Middletown, 1940-1945 (Box 31, Folder 37)
    - Mrs. J.K. Mitchell, 23 Grandview Ave., Middletown, 1940-1941 (Box 31, Folder 38)
    - Mrs. F. Rockwell, 14 William St., Middletown, 1941-1942 (Box 31, Folder 39)
    - Mrs. A. Burkinshaw, Pine Bush, NY, 1940-1941 (Box 31, Folder 40)
    - Mrs. Harry Collins, Warwick, NY, 1940-1942 (Box 31, Folder 41)
    - Family Life Leader: Mrs. Hollis Smith, 120 Orchard St., Monroe, NY, 1940-1941, 1944-1945 (Box 31, Folder 42)
  - Orleans County
    - Orleans County Home Bureau units, 1930-1940 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Mr. Entorf's materials, 1930-1940 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Albion, NY, 1930-1931 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Home Demonstration Agent, 1933-1940 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Home Bureau Unit Reports, 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Home Bureau unit meetings, 1939-1940 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Mrs. Eldridge LaMont, Albion, 1939-1940 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Mrs. Catherine Bartlett, Home Demonstration Agent, 24 Platt, Albion, 1940-1945 (Box 31, Folder 43)
    - Home Bureau, 1940-1945 (Box 31, Folder 44)
    - Holley Mothers' Club, Mrs. Ruth Downey, 1943-1945 (Box 31, Folder 45)
    - Mrs. E.J. Chapman, Albion, NY, 1940-1945 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - West Baire Mothers' Club - Mrs. Lloyd Huber, R.2, Albion, 1940-1945 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Oswego County
    - Home Demonstration Agent, 1933-1940 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Mrs. William J. Potter, Sandy Creek, NY, 1933-1938 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Dr. Lemo Dennis Rockwood's Material, 1935-1936 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Dr. Rockwood's Material, 1936-1937 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Home Bureau Unit Meetings, 1938-1939 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Prof. M. Entorf's Material, 1938-1939 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Lacona and Sandy Creek Group, Mrs. Percy Hotaling, 1938-1939 (Box 3, Folder 47.1)
    - Rosemary Williams, Degeral Bldg., Oswego, 1940-1945 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Home Bureau Reports, 1940-1945 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Mrs. Kenrick D. Foot, 183 East Sixth St., Oswego, NY, 1941-1942 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Otsego County
    - Otsego County - Oneonta, 1929-1930 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - 1930-1931 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Miss Alice V. Bosserman, 1931-1933 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Mrs. Frank Shutts, 1931-1933 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Mrs. H. Fitch, West Oneonta, NY, 1931-1932 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Prof. Entorf's Material, 1936-1939 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - 4-H: Leon McNair, 4-H Club Office, Cooperstown (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Mrs. John Sanyer, Family Life Leader, Otsego County (working in Delaware County) (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Rensselaer County
    - Home Demonstration Agent, 1932-1940 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Mrs. William Wersen, Rensselaer, NY, 1932-1933 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Mrs. H. Winshurst, Rensselaer, 1932-1935 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Mrs. Walter Bell, Rensselaer, 1935-1938 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Mrs. Celanire Bonacker, DeFreesville, NY, 1935-1940 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Mrs. Alden Doolittle, Nassau, NY, 1935-1936 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Mrs. Ida Glady, East Schodack, NY, 1935-1936 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Mrs. Myra Link, Poestenkill, NY, 1935-1939 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Mrs. Rockwood' s material, 1935-1936 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Mrs. Jay Slade, North Hoosick, NY, 1935-1936 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Mrs. H.R. Cranston, R.D., Troy (Betts Corner), 1936-1937 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Mr. Entorf's material, 1936-1939 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Mrs. Arthur Goold, Brookview, NY, 1936-1940 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Mrs. E.J. Hayner, Troy, 1936-1938 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Mrs. George Roller, Troy, 1936-1937 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Mrs. Charles R. Miller, West Sand Eake, NY, 1936-1939 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Mrs. L.M. Nowacki, Schenectady, NY, 1936-1937 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Home Bureau unit meetings, Rensselaer County, 1937-1940 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Mrs. Asa Clyne, Clinton Heights, Rensselaer, 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Mrs. H.R. Cranston, R.D. Troy, 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Mrs. Katherine Stanley, Nassau, 1937-1940 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Mrs. Edward Flynn, Forbes Manor, Rensselaer, 1938-1940 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Miss Lucy Kehn, Lansingburgh, NY, 1938-1939 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Mrs. Harold O'Brien, Troy, 1938-1939 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Mrs. E.W. Quinlivan, Melrose, NY, 1938-1939 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Mrs. Carolyn Thomas, Hoosick Falls, 1938-1940 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Mrs. Charles E. Wagar, Brunswick, NY, 1938-1939 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Rensselaer County Leaders'Enrollment, 1939-1940 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Mrs. E. Crocker, Columbus Heights, Troy, 1939-1940 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Mrs. M. Gardner, Troy, 1939-1940 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Mrs. James Pinney, Schodack Landing, NY, 1939-1940 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Mrs. Edward Quinlivan, Spiegletown Study Group, 1939-1940 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Mrs. J.B. Ryan, Castleton-on-Hudson, NY, 1939-1940 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Mrs. Donald Smith, Rensselaer, 1939-1940 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Mabel A. Milhov, Home Demonstration Agent, P.O. Bldg., Troy, NY, 1940-1945 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Home Bureau, 1940-1945 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Forbes Manor Study Club, Chairman Mrs. Arthur Roy, 369 Morris St., Albany, 1940-1944 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Brookview Study Club, Chairman Mrs. James Gould, Castleton, NY, 1944-1945 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Mrs. J.B. Ryan, Castleton, NY, 1940-1941 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Mrs. Charles Fergason, Clinton Heights Family Life Study Club, 1944-1945 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - East Hoosick Study Club, Mrs. Vincent Alice Le Blanc, Hoosick Falls, R.D. 2, 1944-1945 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Mrs. Carolyn Thomas, Hoosick Falls, NY, 1940-1941 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Mrs. Donald Smith, Rensselaer, NY, 1940-1941 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Mrs. M. Gardner, Rensselaer, 1940-1941 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Mrs. Adam Bonacker, R.D. #1, Rensselaer, 1940-1942 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Mrs. James Pinney, Schodack Landing, NY, 1940-1941 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Mrs. W. Orlo Sylvester, R.D. #4, Troy, 1941-1942 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Red Rock Study Club, Mrs. Florence Pieper, 54 State St., Troy, 1940-1944 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Mrs. W.S. Fletcher, West Sand Lake, NY, 1941-1942 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - White View Child Study Club, Mrs. Eleanor Walter, Wynantskill, NY, 1941-1944 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Rockland County
    - 1936-1937 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - 1938-1939 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - St. Lawrence County
    - Home Demonstration Agent, Canton, NY, 1930-1 940 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Mrs. D. D. Huntress, DeKalb Junction, NY study club, 1931-1940 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Mrs. Harvery Hyde, Ogdensburg, NY study club, 1933-1934 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Mrs. Manford Ottis, Governeur, NY study club, 1934-1936 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Mrs. Hope Lepper, Hialsboro, NY study club, 1935-1936 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Mrs. Clarence Macon, Madrid, NY study club, 1936-1937 (Box 11, Folder -26)
    - Mrs. Grayson, Madrid, NY mother's club, 1937-1938 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Report of Family Life Metting in Home Bureau Unit, 1937-1940 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Mrs. John O'Brien, Ogdensburg, NY, 1938-1939 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Mrs. A. Thompson, Madrid, NY, 1938-1939 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Mr. Entorf, 1938-1939 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Bette Limpert Home Demonstration Agent, Cantrov, Ohio, 1940-1945 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Mrs. Edwin Plant, Madrid, NY, 1940-1943 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Mrs. Lucille Bartholomew, Canton, NY, 1940-1942 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Family Life Study Club, Mrs. Donald Wright, Oswegatchie, 1943-1945 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Home Bureau, 1940-1945 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Mrs. Percibelle Huntress, De Kalb Junction, NY, 1940-1944 (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - Mrs. Evangeline Wright, Nicholville, NY, 1940-1944 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - Saratoga County
    - Mrs. H.A. Jennings, County Leader (Ballston Spa), 1931-1940 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Saratoga Springs, NY, 1930-1931 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Home Demonstration Agent, 1931-1940 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Mrs. Elmer F. Weed, Ballston Spa, NY, 1931-1940 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Mrs. Robert Davis, Ballston Center, 1932-1933 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Mrs. John Heims, Galway, NY, 1932-1940 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Mrs. William Baxter, Ballston Spa, 1933-1935 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Mrs. C.B. Elmore, Saratoga Springs, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Mrs. W. Ernst Spencer, Saratoga Springs, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Mrs. Philip Landry, Saratoga Springs, 1934-1935 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Mrs. Donald Strewer, Ballston Spa Child Study Club, 1934-1935 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Mrs. A. Towers, Porter Corners, 1934-1935 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Mrs. Paul Williams, Burnt Hills, 1934-1936 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Mrs. Gladys Arras, Round Lake, 1935-1940 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Mrs. Norman Jones, Burnt Hills, 1935-1939 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Mrs. Rockwood's materials, 1935-1936 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Mrs. 0. Smears, Wilton, NY, 1935-1937 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Mrs. Edgar L. Cleveland, Ballston Spa Mothers' Club, 1936-1937 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Mr. Entorf's material, 1936-1939 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Mrs. F.W. Droms, Rexford (Clifton Park Study Club), 1937-1940 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Mrs. H.C. Miller, Waterford, NY, 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Mrs. A. Perry, Galway, 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Mrs. Harry Peterson, Corinth, NY, 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Home Bureau unit meetings, 1938-1939 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Mrs. Harold Jennings, Ballston Spa, 1939-1940 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Mrs. E. Nessle, Ballston Lake, 1939-1940 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Estelle E. Jones, Home Demonstration Agent, 87 Church St., Saratoga Springs, NY, 1940-1945 (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Home Bureau, unit reports, etc., 1940-1944 (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - Family Life Leader, Mrs. L.B. Wagner, 1941-1945 (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - Mrs. H. Baldwin, Division St., Ballston Spa, NY, 1940-1942 (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - Milton Adult Child Study Club, Mrs. C.A. Conte, 45 E. High St., Ballston Spa, 1944-1945 (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - Clifton Park Center Study, Mrs. Arthur H. Lockrow, Rexford, NY, 1940-1945 (Box 32, Folder 36)
    - Mrs. Louis Wagman, 75 Ludlow St., Saratoga Springs, NY, 1940-1942 (Box 32, Folder 37)
    - Mrs. H.H. Van Allen, 25 Pinewood Ave., Saratoga Springs, 1940-1942 (Box 32, Folder 38)
    - Mrs. Joseph Kiley, Sarasota Springs, 1940-1941 (Box 32, Folder 39)
    - Mrs. R.W. Kelley, 114 Caroline St., Sarasota Springs, 1940-1941 (Box 32, Folder 40)
    - Mrs. Hilliker, 144 Jefferson St., Sarasota Springs, 1941-1942 (Box 32, Folder 41)
    - Mrs. H.R. Jackson, 205 Broad St., Schuylerville, NY, 1940-1941 (Box 32, Folder 42)
    - Mrs. C. Stewart, South Glens Falls, 1944 (Box 32, Folder 43)
  - Schenectady County
    - Mrs. William Beachner, 1934-1936 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Mrs. Eugena Fink, 1935-1936 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Mrs. John Grant, 1935-1936 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Mrs. O.J. Farrell, 1935-1936 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Mrs. E. L. Handy, 1935-1936 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Mrs. A. J. Muchow, Scotia, NY, 1936-1937 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Mrs. James York, 1936-1937 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - Miss Mary Chaloner, 1451 Parkwood Blvd., Schenectady, NY, 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - Mrs. T. G. Crawford, R.D. #7 Surrey Rd., Schenectady, NY, 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Mrs. Blanche Hedrick, 1938-1939 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Mrs. C. W. Brown, 1414 Belmont Ave., Schenectady, NY, 1938-1939 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Prof. Mark Entorf, 1938-1939 (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - 1939-1940 (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - Clarice Cookingham, Court House, Schenectady, 1940-1945 (Box 32, Folder 44)
    - Home Bureau (unit leaders), 1940-1945 (Box 32, Folder 45)
    - County Leader: Mrs. Fred Wilber, R.D. #2, Delanson, 1944-1945 (Box 32, Folder 46)
    - Schenectady County, 1940-1941 (Box 32, Folder 47)
    - County Leader: Mrs. Eugene Fink, 931 St. David's Lane, Schenectady 8, 1944-1945 (Box 32, Folder 48)
    - Mrs. Ralph E. Wareham, 131 Highland Park Road, Schenectady, 1941-1942 (Box 32, Folder 49)
    - Bellevue Home Bureau Unit, Chairman Mrs. Edward Hanni, 936 Ontario St., Schenectady (Box 32, Folder 50)
    - Iroquois Adult Study Club, Mrs. A.K. Willey 804 Dean St., Schenectady, 1944-1945 (Box 32, Folder 51)
    - Schohanna Child Life Study Club, Mrs. Francis Crowe, Quaker St., 1944-1945 (Box 32, Folder 52)
  - Schoharie County
    - Helen Brougham, Home Demonstration Agent, Cobleskill, NY, 1944-1945 (Box 32, Folder 53)
    - Schuyler County (Box 32, Folder 54)
    - Burdett Mothers' Club, Mrs. Florence Phelps, Hector, NY, 1944-1945 (Box 32, Folder 55)
  - Schuyler County
    - Miss Constance La Bagh, 1931-1933 (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - Mrs. Allan Booth, Odessa, NY, 1935-1936 (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - Prof. Mark Entorf, 1936-1937 (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - Prof. Mark Entorf, 1938-1939 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Seneca County
    - Seneca County, 1943 (Box 32, Folder 56)
  - Steuben County
    - Home Demonstration Agents, 1930-1940 (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - Mrs. D. A. Neu, 1931-1933 (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - Mrs. Margaret Gibbs, 1931-1932 (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - Mrs. Arch Sandford, Hammondsport, NY, 1931-1932 (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - Dr. Anna Viele, Hornell, NY, 1931-1932 (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - Mrs. E. Overhiser, Savona, NY, 1931-1932 (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - Mrs. Ethel Stewart, Howard, NY, 1931-1933 (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - Mrs. Leon Riker, Addison, NY, 1932-1933 (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - Home Bueau Unit Meetings, 1939-1940 (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - Mrs. Sheldon Stewart, Addison, NY, 1939-1940 (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - Mrs. Elroy Hannahs, Addison, NY, 1939-1940 (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - Mrs. Lois D. Mathewson, County Clerk's Bldg., Bath, NY, 1940-1945 (Box 32, Folder 57)
    - Home Bureau Unit, 1940-1944 (Box 32, Folder 58)
    - Mothers' Club, Mrs. R. Wickinson, Addison, NY, 1941-1945 (Box 32, Folder 59)
    - Mrs. Carl Abbott, 339 E. High St., Painted Post, 1940-1941 (Box 32, Folder 60)
  - Suffolk County
    - Suffolk County - Riverhead, 1929-1930 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Suffolk County - Southhampton, 1929-1930 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Suffolk County, Riverhead, NY, 1930-1931 (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - Mrs. Clyde looker, Riverhead, NY, 1931-1933 (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - Mrs. Paul Nugent, Easthampton, NY, 1931-1934 (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - Mrs. J. Harold Downs, Riverhead, NY, 1931-1934 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Mrs. Joseph Payne, Quogue, NY, 1934-1935 (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - Mrs. W. D. Buckingham. Southampton, NY, 1934-1937 (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - Home Demonstration Agent, 1931-1940 (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - Prof. Mark Entorf's Material, 1938-1939 (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - Home Bureau Unit Meetings, 1939-1940 (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - Mrs. Vera Brush, Court House, Riverhead, 1940-1945 (Box 32, Folder 61)
    - Home Bureau Unit, 1940-1944 (Box 32, Folder 62)
    - Family Life Leader: Mrs. Walter Been, 505 Elton St., Riverhead, 1941-1945 (Box 32, Folder 63)
    - Mrs. C.G. Pohle, Family Life Leader, 800 Washington Drive, Huntington, NY (Box 32, Folder 64)
    - Mrs. Maynard Hende, 4-H Club Office, Riverhead, 1942-1943 (Box 32, Folder 65)
    - The Family Forum Study Club, Chairman Elsie Wells, Elton St., Riverhead, 1940-1945 (Box 32, Folder 66)
  - Sullivan County
    - Sullivan County, 1930-1931 (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Tioga County
    - Oswego, NY Study Club, 1931-1932 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Miss Mary R. Evans, Home Demonstration Agent, 1932-1940 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Miss Rockwood, 1936-1937 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Mrs. Dorothy Lane, Lounsberry, NY, 1939-1940 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Care of Children at Meetings, Mrs. D. Leas, 1940-1942 (Box 32, Folder 67)
    - Ethel McDonald, Home Demonstration Agent, Owego, NY, 1940-1945 (Box 32, Folder 68)
    - Home Bureau Reports, 1940-1945 (Box 32, Folder 69)
    - Mrs. Ethel McNeil, Lounsberry, NY, 1940-1943 (Box 32, Folder 70)
  - Tompkins County
    - Tompkins County - Ithaca, 1929-1930 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Ithaca, NY, 1931-1940 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Development Association, 1936 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Mr. Entorf, 1936-1937 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Mrs, M. Galbreath, Brooktondale, NY study club, 1937-1938 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Mr. Entorf, 1938-1939 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Unit Leader Reports, 1938-1939 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Mrs. George Robinson, Chairman, Ithaca, NY study club, 1938-1939 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Mrs. Raymond Johnson, Chariman, slatersville, NY study club, 1938-1939 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Mrs. R. R. Rightmyer, Chairman, Bethel Grove, NY study club, 1938-1939 (Box 11, Folder -44)
    - Mrs. F. Painter, Chairman, Ithaca, NY study club, 1939-1940 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Untitled, 1939-1940 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Home Bureau Unit Meetings, 1939-1940 (Box 11, Folder 47)